What the hell
are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait.
West! You bastard!
I win the game
for you today,
and you're
screwing my wife?!
West,
are you okay?
Ted,
what's wrong with you?
What?
I'm working my ass off
and you're here cheating,
doing drugs and...
screwing someone
in my house
and you're asking
me what's wrong?
You think that
I cheated for fun?
It's because
you're a loser.
Thirty-two years old and
you can't even
pay the damn bills.
My friends all
live in mansions
and drive fancy cars
and I'm stuck with
a loser like you.
I got a raise.
I came here to
tell you this...
We don't have to worry
about the bills anymore.
A raise?
You're an
assistant coach.
What could you
possibly make?
Three grand?
Two, actually.
Tell me, Ted,
when am I
supposed to get
my mansion and my fancy car
on that salary?
Emma, I... I was
gonna make it happen.
You're never gonna
make it happen.
You're fired.
What?
No, you can't do this. I...
I won the game
for you today.
If it wasn't for me,
the team wouldn't
even be here, okay?
I'm the head coach.
A busted leg loser
like you
deserves nothing.
But to be crushed
under someone
like me.
West's right, your
whole month's salary
couldn't buy
one of his belts.
Thinking you could
give me a rich life?
Keep dreaming.
Divorce Agreement?
You already
had this ready?
Well, now that
you caught us,
what's the point
of hiding it?
It's signed.
Come on, babe.
Let's go.
Who's calling this trash?
Don't tell me it's
some telemarketer.
All he should
worry about
is unemployment
insurance.
Fuck off.
Twenty-five thousand
passing yards,
front-runner for
the Heisman.
Are you really gonna
end your career as
an assistant coach?
Is that what you want
your legacy to be?
Who is this?
Mr. Vincent,
this is Grace Taylor,
owner of the Knights.
I'd like to offer
you the position of
head coach.
Annual salary is
a million dollars.
How's that?